A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.9-RG 1.15 (A83-A89) FA479
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 89), 1973-1991; bulk; 1.15; 44.4 Cubic Feet; Standard record storage boxes - Box R2412-Box R2448.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF)
    - RF 85069 National Urban League - Permanent development fund, 1985-1989 (Box R2446)
    - RF 85078 - A115 Tufts University - Geographic medicine, 1977-1987 (Box R2446)
    - RF 85088 Urban Affairs Partnership - Philadelphia schools and humanities, 1983-1987 (Box R2447)
    - RF 86021 Guttmacher Institute - Adolescent pregnancy, 1978-1988 (Box R2448)